Practical significance is useful not only
实际显著性不仅有助于
for making a decision at the end of the experiment,
在实验结束时做出决策
but also for actually setting up the experiment scope.
而且有助于设置实验范围
Let's consider an AB test where we want to see if changing
举个 A/B 测试的例子
the layout of a homepage brings more visitors to a digital storefront.
假设我们想观察首页布局变化是否会使更多人访问在线商店
The current click-through rate is 10 percent and the practical significance boundary we
当前的点击率为 10% 我们希望新布局
want to see what the new layout is a twopercent absolute increase to 12 percent.
达到的实际显著性界限为上升 2% 使点击率达到 12%
How many data points do we need to record in
我们需要记录多少数据点
order to reliably detect that kind of change?
才能可靠地检测到这种变化？
The concept you should recall here is statistical power.
这时候要用到的一个概念是统计功效
Power is the probability that a hypothesis test will
功效是指假设检验实际检测到
actually detect a particular true mean as different from the null.
特定真实均值而非零值的概率
The curves on these two plots represent
右侧的两个曲线图表示
the expected distribution of the difference in sample
对照组和实验组中
means given 1,000 observations in each of the control group and experimental group.
1,000 个观察对象的样本均值预期分布差异
The top curve gives the distribution of differences
上图表示新布局没有效果时的
if there was no effect on the new layout,
差异分布图
and the bottom curve gives the distribution of differences
下图表示假设点击率按预期上升 2% 后
assuming our desired two percent increase in click-through rate.
差异分布情况
On the top curve, a vertical line indicates
在上图中 竖线表示
the critical value for a type one error rate of five percent.
I 型错误率 5% 的临界值
Matching this critical value from the null hypothesis curve down to
将零假设曲线中的该临界值
the desired alternative hypothesis curve allows us to see
与下方的替代性期望假设曲线相匹配
the power on the right of the line and the type two error rate on the left.
使我们能够得出竖线右侧的功效以及左侧的 II 型错误率
Increasing the number of data points will narrow
增加数据点将使两条曲线变窄
both curves, increasing statistical power.
并提高统计功效
If we want a power of 0.8,
如果我们希望功效为 0.8
or in other words, an 80 percent chance of rejecting the null,
换句话说 拒绝零值的概率为 80%
assuming a 12 percent true click-through rate,
假设真实点击率为 12%
then we need at least 2,863
那么对照组和实验组
observations in each of our control group and experimental group.
分别至少需要 2,863 个观察对象
We can then refer to our website's daily traffic
然后 我们可以根据网站的每日流量
to figure out about how long we should run the experiment.
得出实验应该运行多长时间
If we have about 500 visitors per day,
假设每天有 500 名访问者
then this means that we should run the experiment for about 12 days.
那么实验应该运行大约 12 天
Perhaps rounding up to a full two weeks to try and
或许可以四舍五入到两周时间
reduce potential effects of weekly cycles.
这样可以降低星期循环的潜在影响
After collecting data for this predetermined time period,
按照提前确定的期限收集数据后
we can then analyze the data to see the effectiveness of the website layout change.
我们可以分析数据 看看网站布局变化的效果
Checking for the expected experiment length is important since you
按照预期的时长运行实验很重要
want to be able to act on your findings while they're still relevant.
因为你希望在结果依然相关时采取行动
If you find that the required time for a design is too long,
如果你发现实验所需的时间太长
then you might need to change statistical parameters.
那么可能需要更改统计参数
This might meet increasing the practical significance boundary or
例如提高实际显著性的界限
focusing your design into different metrics or populations.
或者将实验分成多个指标或总体
This will reduce variability in order to shorten the study to a more reasonable length.
这样可以降低变化性 并将研究缩短为合理的时长